[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ceausescu"], "LOCATION": ["Romania", "Berlin"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Have you seen anything quite like this in your entire career?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "The last time I saw something like this was in Romania when Ceausescu was overthrown and the Berlin Wall coming down shortly before that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "How did you feel when you heard President Mubarak stepped down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "I couldn't believe it, I was emotional, I cried actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "How did you feel when you heard President Mubarak had stepped down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "It's a bit festive (ph) to Egypt today.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Can you trust them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Yes, I can trust them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Because they came up (INAUDIBLE).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["70 percent", "80 percent"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "So, that's what you need to hear from the army next, those clear steps toward democracy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I'm sure about 70 percent or 80 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "How long is the party going to go on for tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "The party is not for tonight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Arwa, extraordinary scenes there with Egyptians that are having this incredible day in their lives, what you experiencing where you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Piers, it's truly been a remarkable experience, a remarkable moment to witness in history, not just for Egyptians but for the entire region as a whole.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tahrir Square", "Facebook"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Why did you choose to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Because everybody here, they need the (AUDIO BREAK) we met here in Tahrir Square from Facebook, everybody they met on Facebook first, and then we took the position to come here and meet here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Could it be that because we now have Omar Suleiman, who many people believe has been effectively running this regime anyway for the last two years, that we're out of the frying pan into the fryer a bit here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, I don't want to be a killjoy because obviously people are savoring the joy of this moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last two years"], "PERSON": ["Omar Suleiman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "What are you feeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "I spent a few moments, a few minutes in disbelief and I couldn't say anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Do you believe that the Egyptian military is on the people's side?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "IRGANY: It's very difficult to speculate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "It's been an extraordinary example of people power taking on a regime that it no longer wanted in government and beating it, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, certainly, this is unprecedented -- not only in Egypt but in the region, and I dare say in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "I mean, do you feel exhilarated, or do you feel slightly apprehensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "How quickly do you think you can get Egypt's economy going again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Well, I think surprisingly, we were able to manage the crisis very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Finally, Dr. Radwan, will you be celebrating this evening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "I will be celebrating the fact that Egypt has never done the road of chaos, that this country has been protected and we hope that the transition would take place to a democratic Egypt in the future.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Radwan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "And what do you think happens now in terms of the politics here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "It is a fascinating moment and an unpredictable moment, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "We are trying to crack that code and I know you have two gentlemen behind me next in the program who have been involve in the sensitive diplomacy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "John, finally, how do you think that President Obama has handled this crisis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Well, it's rocky and again, you have two veteran diplomats behind me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "What do you think with all your expertise, the implications both for the region and specifically for Israel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, it's cataclysmic for the region.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richardson"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "When you see regime change coming from the bottom up like this, in a peaceful series of increasingly large protests by the people, is that not the way to go in terms of American foreign policy, encourage people to take action like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Of course, this is the best way for change to happen and I believe that this is a historic development as Governor Richardson said for the whole region.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Mr. Baer, let me ask you straight away: is this democracy we're seeing here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "That's not the way I see it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Baer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Omar Suleiman"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "The question is how long will he last in that role?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Tell me about Omar Suleiman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Is he now in charge of the military?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "He's a former general.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "So this may just be the beginning of further turmoil in Egypt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "I think absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "If you were still a CIA operative, what do you think the top brass at the CIA would be most concerned about from what they're witnessing tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RBS", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I think what they should be concerned about is the army holds together.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA", "CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["PLO"], "PERSON": ["Mahmoud Abbas"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "It's a good example for them, because then what they're saying is look, we can overthrow the PLO, Mahmoud Abbas, as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What kind of a man is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "He's very suave and sophisticated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "So are we really in a situation where it's just the same kind of thing in a different face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "He's certainly not a new face to anybody who's followed things closely behind the scenes in Egypt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Or are they in charge of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "There's a lot to still be sorted out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Finally, and perhaps most crucially, Jane, if I had said to you five years ago, right, I have found the guy who's going to bring pure democratic freedom to Egypt and his name is Omar Suleiman, how would you have reacted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "RBS", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Well, unless he's going through some sort of tremendous personal transformation, it would have been laughable really.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["five years ago"], "PERSON": ["Jane", "Omar Suleiman"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Do you believe it will now change for the better, from what you have seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJR", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I think something's broken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Do you believe what we heard earlier in the program, that he may be part of some coup d'etat by the military here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Personally, as an Egyptian, I don't trust him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "But a great day for Egypt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "An amazing day, a momentous day.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "An emotional day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Extremely emotional.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mana"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "What are your views on that, as somebody who's been involved in very different kinds of regime changes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I think it was Mana who said earlier the barrier of fear has been broken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Saddam"], "LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "When you compare what's happened here to what happened in Iraq, do you not think, with the benefit of hindsight, that the kind of devastation we saw in the aftermath of the Iraq war could possibly have been avoided if we had just waited and encouraged the people of Iraq to do what the people of Egypt have done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Piers, you may forget, but exactly 20 years ago, we encouraged the people of Iraq to rise up against Saddam and he slaughtered tens of thousands of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq", "Iraq", "Iraq", "Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "And it's that spirit of peace, that they wouldn't be provoked into violence, that has really moved the entire world, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I mean, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams that you would see democracy come so fast?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "When we were making that film, we could only dream of something like this happening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]